[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)[Limited time only!

Code: GIFT](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/christmas-sale)

10 November 2023 Version 2.0

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data when you use our Service. We also explain the choices you have in relation to this information. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data. Find out what that means.

1\. What data do we collect and how do we use them?
---------------------------------------------------

We process a few different types of information for different purposes as explained below.  

### Personal Data

(a) In order to provide our Service to you we process:  

* Your name and email address;
* HTTPS requests to our Services, data destinations, and timestamps; however, we do not keep a record of the websites you visit, your IP address, the volume or nature of your network traffic, the content of any communications you make, or the duration of your online sessions.

(b) To manage payments for the Services we process your payment and transaction information (such as the name of the bank which issued the credit card uses for payments, partial credit card information, credit card’s owner’s full name, address, email,  chargebacks requests, cancelled orders and other information requested by legitimate our payment processors).  
  
(c) For security monitoring, performance optimisation, debugging and troubleshooting, fraud detection and other operational intelligence purposes, we may collect and process our server logs containing your IP address, browser type, timestamp, and request URI; however, we cannot associate such data with you personally. This means that the such data is used in a way that doesn't allow us to identify who you are specifically. The information is typically aggregated or anonymized for analysis, so it serves a functional purpose without compromising your personal privacy.  
  
(d) For the purposes of communicating with you and providing support, we process your email and communication information (e.g. content of your emails).  
  
If you consent, we may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. In such case we process your email. You may withdraw your consent to receive any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.  

### Personal Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and we hold certain information.  
  
Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Other tracking technologies such as beacons, tags and scripts are used to collect and track information to analyse and improve our Service.  
  
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some aspects of our Service.  
  
Examples of Cookies we use:  

* Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
* Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
* Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
* Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.

2\. Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data
--------------------------------------------

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific purpose for which we process it.  
  
We process your Personal Data because:  

* We need to perform a contract with you
* You have given us permission to do so
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it is not overridden by your rights
* To comply with the law

3\. Retention of Data
---------------------

We will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with  legal obligations (for example, applicable tax calculation), resolve disputes and enforce our legal agreements and policies.  

4\. Transfer of data
--------------------

Your personal data will not be sold or otherwise transferred to third parties without a legitimate basis, as well as used for purposes other than those for which they were collected. We will not transfer your personal data in any way other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy or applicable law.  
  
We may transfer your Personal Data to companies that help us operate, i.e. data processors. We require these data processors to process your data only in accordance with our instructions and applicable data protection legislation. We enter into agreements with these data processors that require the parties to comply strictly with the requirements of personal data protection.  
  
We may share your Personal Data with third party service providers whose services we typically use for payment processing, data storage, website hosting and other services, or service providers such as debt collection companies or companies providing archiving services, including legal/marketing service providers.  
  
Below is the list of the service providers which we employ:  

Google Analytics

Google Tag Manager

Microsoft Clarity

Facebook

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads, follow these instructions from Facebook; read more about Facebook’s Data Policy

Linkedin

Please read more about Linkedin marketing solutions at You can opt out of LinkedIn data collection and targeting cookies following the instructions here.

Reddit

Please learn more about Reddit remarketing tools and how to opt out by visiting this page.

X Corp.

Information about the data processing performed by X Corp. and the corresponding purposes pursued can be found in the data protection guidelines of X Corp.:  
[https://twitter.com/privacy](http://‍https://twitter.com/privacy)It is possible for you to restrict the processing of your data by X. For that purpose, you can open the general settings of your X account and change your privacy settings.

Typeform

Typeform service provided by TYPEFORM S. L. We use Typeform for conducting the surveys. For more information about Typeform's data processing, please refer to:  

X Corp.

Information about the data processing performed by X Corp. and the corresponding purposes pursued can be found in the data protection guidelines of X Corp.:  
[https://twitter.com/privacy](http://‍https://twitter.com/privacy)It is possible for you to restrict the processing of your data by X. For that purpose, you can open the general settings of your X account and change your privacy settings.

Typeform

Typeform service provided by TYPEFORM S. L. We use Typeform for conducting the surveys. For more information about Typeform's data processing, please refer to:  

Intercom

Intercom service is provided by Intercom, Inc. We use Intercom for communication and analytics purposes. For more information on what type of information Intercom collects, see Intercom Terms and Policies:  

Mailchimp

Mailchimp service is provided by The Rocket Science Group LLC. We use Mailchimp for marketing messages distribution purposes. For more information on the privacy practices of Mailchimp, visit their Privacy Policy:  

AppsFlyer

We use AppsFlyer for analytics purposes, please refer to:  

Sentry

We use Sentry for technical purposes, please refer to the privacy policy:  

In some cases, your data may be transferred to the third countries where other personal data protection regulations may apply. We have taken appropriate safeguards (e.g. Model Contract Clauses) to ensure that your personal data remains protected, and we require that our third-party service providers and partners also have appropriate safeguards in place.  

5\. Disclosure of data
----------------------

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of assets, your Personal  Data may be transferred. We will notify you before your Personal  Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
  
We may disclose your Personal Data if we belief in good faith that such action is necessary to:  

* Comply with a legal obligation.
* Protect and defend our rights or property.
* Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with our Service.
* Protect the personal safety of users of our Service and/or the general public.
* Protect us against legal liability.

6\. Security of Data
--------------------

The security of your data is important to us. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage that is 100% secure.  
  
While we strive to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  

7\. Your Data Protection Rights
-------------------------------

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. We aim to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete or limit the use of your Personal Data.  
  
If you would like to know what Personal Data we hold about you and to have it removed from our systems, please contact us.  
  
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:  

* The right to access, update or delete the information we hold about you. Wherever possible, you can access, update or request the deletion of your Personal Data directly from your account settings. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us for assistance.
* The right to rectification. You have the right to have your Personal Data corrected if it is inaccurate or incomplete.
* The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
* The right to restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your Personal Data.
* The right to data portability. You have the right to receive a copy of the information we hold about you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
* The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where we rely on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.  
  
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).  

8\. Links to Other Sites
------------------------

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. When you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policy of each site you visit.  
  
We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.  

9\. Children’s privacy
----------------------

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).  
  
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us.  
  
If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from Children without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information from our servers.  

10\. Changes to this Privacy Policy
-----------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.  
  
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.  
  
We recommend that you review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.  

11\. Contact Us
---------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact us by emailing: [help@mysteriumvpn.com](http://help@mysteriumvpn.com/)  

12\. Definitions
----------------

Us”, “we”, or “our”  
  
This refers to UAB “MN Technologijos”, a company incorporated in the Republic of Lithuania, legal entity code 304869871.  
Registered office: Konstitucijos pr. 21A,  LT-08130, Vilnius, Lithuania.  
  
“Service” is the [https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/](https://www.mysteriumvpn.com/) website operated by us.  
  
“Personal Data” means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).  
  
“Usage Data” is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).  
  
“Cookies” are small files stored on your device (computer or mobile device).  
  
“Data Controller” means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.  
  
“Data Processor (or Service Provider)” means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.  
  
“Data Subject” is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.  

Get the next-generation of ethical VPN technology. A decentralized VPN is powered by a global community.

Platforms

VPN for everyone

Resources

Contact us

Newsletter

Get the latest tips, updates and exclusive VPN deals.

Check this box if you agree to receive infrequent emails & promotions from the Mysterium VPN team

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

© Copyright 2024 UAB "MN Technologijos"
